HELLO

Jeffrey Huysentruyt

Creative Director & UI/UX Designer

I am a digital craftsman who creates beautiful and intuitive user interfaces. Being a creative director and UI/UX designer with over 10 years of experience, I know how to fuel freelance relationships, high impact startups and creative agencies. I have a strong passion for leading teams to create amazing products and brands with a human-centered design approach.

SKILLS

Branding

Design Leadership

Product Architecture

Responsive Design

UI/UX Design

SAY HEY

- → (810) 300-6165
- → sweetlookingstuff@gmail.com
- → iamjeffrey.design

EXPERIENCE

Director of Digital Design

Bluewater | May 2018 - Present

As the director of digital design, I lead a team of designers to create interactive content for displays, both large and small. I am also designing an IoT software platform to manage and monitor devices, in addition to leading a rebrand effort, including a fresh color palette, an all new web presence and updated branded materials.

Creative Director & Executive Board Member

Career Now Brands/CDL Marketing | April 2017 - May 2018

As the creative director, I led a team of designers to create many digital products, as well as supporting branding and marketing materials. I was also an active member of the executive board, planning the future direction of the company.

Lead Designer

LevelEleven | June 2015 - April 2017

Being the lead designer, I was in charge of producing our product's graphic presentation, including its reactivity and interactivity in response to a user's input across different display environments.

Graphic & Web Designer

Element5 | August 2013 - June 2015

At this agency, I worked for a variety of clients, all of whom had different needs: websites, photography, packaging, videos, logos, and more.

Graphic Designer

Synectics Media | April 2011 - August 2013

I created websites, logos, videos, photography and other designed materials for many different clients.

EDUCATION

Bacholor of Arts in Graphic Design

Lawrence Technological University | 2007 - 2011

SOFTWARE

FIGMA SKETCH INVISION ZEPLIN

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE JIRA WRIKE

SLACK G SUITE